hello to us people,
нам людей здравствуй
so we agreed
вот мы и сошлись
who we are
кто мы
two flags behind us so what and what
два флага позади нас так и что и что
now
теперь
but exactly the expenses from ukraine you are from where the
но именно расходы из украины вы откуда
games are speed which region is
игры скорость какая область
novosibirsk novosibirsk and the city of
новосибирская новосибирск а город
buildings above has already been renamed
корпусов выше так уже переименовали
recently
недавно
ukrainian from the city more than the original
украинской из города больше изначальному
but now it’s like headphones  the highest
но сейчас как то наушниками высшего
is called because it hasn’t given anyone zero
называется ведь никому не zero вали
so far, but
дала до сих пор а
it was still Kuibyshev Samara up to
это же еще был куйбышев самара до
three hundred years already noted in this seriously
трёхсот лет уже отметили в этом серьезно
there was an anniversary around you this year plus
вокруг вас был юбилей в этом году плюс
paste over answered but look how you feel
оклеить ответили а вот смотрите как вы
about the war in Ukraine,
относитесь к войне в украине
as it were, of course
как бы обязательно конечно
it’s wrong that Putin led the troops
неправильно что путин вел войска
neutrally done
нейтрально сделано
he
он
got what he did well Putin turns out to
получил что сделал ну путин получается
be wrong to do that he led troops to
не правильно сделать что вел войска в
ukraine
украину
why was it wrong to remove this is a
почему неправильно убрали это это
forced measure you are negative or you
вынужденная мера вы отрицательно или вы
say that this is a forced measure a
говорите что это вынужденная мера
forced measure is so forced than it
вынужденная мера так вынуждена чем она
was forced and
была вынуждена и
I then war  I don’t want neither and I just don’t
я то войны не хочу ни и я просто не хочу
want people to die and war implies
чтобы люди погибали а война предполагает
that people  and they die, it
что люди погибают
turns out why Putin attacked Ukraine
получается зачем путин напал на украину
and
и
that I, too, will go to my category a1 and
что я тоже пойду у меня категория а1 и
tyler read the category above and who are you by the
тайлер читай выше категорию а кто вы по
type of troops
роду войск
marines marines
морская пехота морская пехота
naples will be much easier
неаполь куда легче будет
now, having washed out, somehow, the
теперь вымыв ну как-то уже морская
marines are no longer solid in  you
пехота уже не не солидно в россии
take out Russia after you sank the
вынимаете после того как потопили
flagship of the Black Sea Fleet, the cruiser
флагман черноморского флота крейсер
Moscow, as if
москва как
from a serpentine island, they drove away a
с острова змеиный прогнали как тапками
Russian
русский
journalist like slippers at the bottom, and nevertheless,
журналист дне ну и не менее тем не менее
anyway, well, agree, popular
все равно в это ну согласитесь популярны
Russia, which has such a huge
россии у которой есть такой огромный
slot
слот
to lose the flagship of the frog fleet in the fight against
потерять флагман frog флота в борьбе с
Ukraine  which has no fleet at all,
украиной у которой флота вообще нет
almost even if it’s a shame to agree
почти даже если это позор согласить
why
почему позу
they pose as something like a group, well, how are you, in
они чем-то группу ну так а как ты по
fact, the flagship the flagship,
сути флагман флагман
I’m a huge howl, not just a huge one,
я огромный вой не то что просто огромную
how many escorts he has and then
сколько у него сопровождение и тогда
he was knocked out
его подбили
because
так как так как
since half an
по полу
hour  snake countries why such an honor
часа стран змеиный почему такого честь
our Ukrainians in the hall points of the
украинцы наши в зале пункты
background, but there were no such
подоплека же не было таких подоплека
elementary reasons for our side, let's say
элементарных нашу сторону допустим
nothing of the sort  it wasn’t just a
ничего такого не было просто вот из вашу
miracle woman from your side, well, why
сторону чудо-баба ну а зачем зачем
did Russia attack Ukraine at all, why does
вообще россия напала на украину зачем
your glue die for what is
ради чего умирает ваши клей
it called when one country sends
как называется когда одна страна вводит
its troops into another country an invasion attack
свои войска в другую страну нападение
or it can’t be about non-aggression what
or же не может быть о ненападении чем
is the difference between an invasion and an attack  I understood
отличается вторжение от нападения понял
but these are different things
но это разные вещи
forced the world and because you have to
вынуждены мир и потому что у вас
save
избавить
Nazism,
нацизм
that is, it turns out you invaded
то есть получается вы вторглись в
Ukraine made an invasion to
украину сделали вторжение чтобы
liberate one price
освободить одна цена
bombed 8 years turned on so
бомбили 8 лет включила так
why not but
почему не так а
motorola on
motorola на погибли
matera died this is some kind of dodik from Russia
матера это какой-то из россии
came and pike
приехал и пику
he
он
is a Russian himself, why did he come to
сам россиянин почему он приперся в
ukraine besides and closed his eyes, so what
украину помимо и зажмурили ну и что
to take away and why was he a Russian infantryman in ukraine
отвести а чё он был в украине русский
and look at
пехотинец а у
them
них
what you will be from russia they
смотри какие то будете из россии
came started in ukraine in the world
приехали начали в украине в мире
from underhand their own and yes probably
из-подтишка свои же причем да наверно
yours in the showdown of gangster
ваши в разборках бандитских
look at the
смотрите
lawlessness of the bandit DPR and LPR, but
беспредел бандитский днр и лнр а вот
look how you think Russia is a rich
смотрите как вы считаете россия богатая
country rich enough to eat gold ours goes out
на богатую достаточно есть золото гаснет
where does the money from
вас нет и столько ресурса вот у вас вы
all these resources go?
всей европе продаете на европа звезды
czech republic has no resources she buys gas from
чехии нет ресурсов она покупает газ у
russia pays russia granny ethics
россии платит россии бабуль этики
russia gathers all european grandmas but a
россия собирается всей европы бабки но
man in the czech republic lives better than a resident of
мужик в чехии живет лучше чем у житель
novosibirsk why who then steals
новосибирске почему кто кто тогда ворует
all this money from the gas
все эти деньги из газа
who is it
кто это
coming up there something
подходишь там что-то
to the nose but
к носу но
whose name is not allowed  to call out loud, yes,
чье имя нельзя называть вслух да
just
просто
someone should snatch out who is stealing all
кто-то должен вырвать кто это ворует все
such huge grandmothers,
такие огромные бабки
officials there also play their role until it
чиновники там тоже играю свою роль до на
turns out that Putin and his colleagues are
получается что путин и его коллеги в
robbing you of all the
обворовывают вас все
words of Putin
слова путин
out and they are pleased with me, killing them like that, and
вон и их радуют я куста них таких убив а
there and that's right  inevitably, the
вон и вот правильно неизбежно на поляну
Russians will rob you into a clearing wedge to cultivate a beggar in a
клину русские вас грабят возделать нищий
huge rich country and
огромную богатую страну и так и
distract you by fighting in
отвлекают вас тем что надо воевать в
Ukraine with some mythical Nazis,
украине с каким-то мифическими нацистами
that is, instead of going out  to a
то есть ты вместо того чтобы выходить на
rally for the fact that where is the money from our
митинг за то что где деньги от нашего
oil and gas sends you to die in
нефтегаза так тебя отправляет сдохнуть в
Ukraine
украину
dudes in the Kremlin sit their children travel
чуваки в кремле сидят ихние детки ездит
around Europe sorry
по европам sorry
think
думай
and try to channel like Crimea
и пытайтесь на канал ставьте лайк крым